{
    "id": "1ec8dc29e40641589f4a4eac0f7991fa",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We had an invite …………………………. could not gain admittance anyhow.",
            "description": "Use but to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "however",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "cdb62d6bc9804975804ae1e30848da66"
        },
        {
            "question": "As he ………………………. older, he started forgetting things.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "got",
                "gets",
                "has gotten"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "90512b6f6c144d6696c715bd2408a996"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………….. anything I have ever done.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have never regretted",
                "had never regretted",
                "am never regretting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fbb0eff0ec8c4d78acd8763d2877c59d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was made ………………………………. .",
            "description": "When make is used in the passive form, it is followed by an infinitive with to. ",
            "answers": [
                "apologize",
                "to apologize",
                "apologizing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2687342ac3d14941be2b97dbc62b5905"
        },
        {
            "question": "Climbing mountains ……………………………. good for health.",
            "description": "Here the subject is the ing form climbing. Ing forms are treated as singular. ",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e7d20a1f5d86498d8b74775213f0c3b7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sam as well his friends ……………………….. at the party.",
            "description": "When we connect a singular and plural noun with as well as, the verb agrees with the former. ",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "83a3f27459a949109e07ff13b12bf691"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sam along with his life and children ………………………… in that apartment.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "lives"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ad62b54356dc44aab1c06ce2857f86d9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you know who ………………………….?",
            "description": "In indirect questions, the subject goes before the auxiliary verb.",
            "answers": [
                "is she",
                "she is"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c5fbef576d674f58aca21d5f6fc8cda5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Hardly …………………………. out when it started raining again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "had I stepped",
                "did I step",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "894c7e1c5cda4de58643a95c43a26e39"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am anxious ………………………….. his safety.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "of",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d7106c5eb5a84e5a9431ad2eb7bb0fb2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Each guest ………………………. arrived.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb with each and every. ",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have",
                "is"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ca12dc23cc3e45bcb73b2d4a3019d762"
        },
        {
            "question": "Every student …………………….. to hand in their work before Friday.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after every. ",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3ed034b6691e4894894b9c5d45be5ee8"
        }
    ]
}